steves-internet-guide.com 2016-05-14

# Privacy Policy

We takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.

### Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, **This site** uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information.

Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

In particular this site use Google Adsense and,

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html)

### Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. This list of [ web browser privacy management](http://www.synclastic.com/privacy/browser-configuration/) links may also be useful.

### Email Addresses

Our site’s registration and contact forms require that you enter your email address and contact name and other such information. This information is used to send out our electronic newsletter, query responses and other information about other products and services offered by the website **steves-internet-guide.com**.

**We will not give away or sell your email address**. In the event that this website is sold you will be given 1 month advance notice and the option to remove yourself from the email list.

**You are free to opt out of the list at any time**!

### How You Can Correct or Remove Information

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please click on this link and/or use our Contact Us page.

### Updates and Effective Date

( **steves-internet-guide.com** ) reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

### Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to ( **steves-internet-guide.com** ‘s) Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

### Contact Information

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to the webmaster by using the [contact form](http://www.steves-internet-guide.com/about/).

**Was This Article Helpful? Please Rate..**

[Total: 0    Average: 0/5]
